## **Troy Harris**

Phone: (209)303-7172

Email: troymichael222@gmail.com

## **Summary:**

I am twenty-six years old and I can make a superior addition to your workforce. I have three years experience working as an electronics repair technician. My tasks include diagnosing and fixing cell phones, tablets, laptops, and game consoles. I'm currently managing three employees at my store. As the manager, I consistently exceed all our monthly goals and quotas. My team provides excellent customer service to all our guests. I love working in a fast paced environment because it keeps my mind sharp and motivated.

I also have three years experience as a construction laborer. My duties included driving a truck with a trailer attached, cleaning up work sites, purchasing material, communicating with homeowners, handling power tools and demolition. I'm incredibly crafty with my hands and I love to learn new skills.

## **Qualifications:**

- 3+ years experience as an electronics repair technician
- 3+ years experience as a construction laborer
- 10+ years experience as a customer service rep
- 10+ years experience driving class C license with a clean record

## Employment history:

Repair All Phone Repair in Modesto, CA

Employment from October 2017 to present day

**Responsibilities**: customer service, supervisor, audit inventory, time management

Brawley Construction Co. in Ripon, CA

Employment from August 2014 to September 2017

**Responsibilities**: laborer, drive truck with trailer, power tools, remodeling, demolition

Mountain Mike's Pizza in Modesto, CA

Employment from September 2010 to July 2014

**Responsibilities:** delivery driver, customer service, time management, audit inventory